

CONTACT ME AT

- - +6019-602 1939
- - syahirzakwanyusof@gmail.com
- www.syahirzakwan. infinityfreeapp.com
- 9
- Klang, Selangor
- @syhrzkwn

LANGUAGE I SPEAK

- •••• Bahasa Malaysia
- •••• English

SKILLS

- •••• Forward-Looking
- •••• Teamwork
- •••• Critical Thinking
- •••• Problem Solving

PROGRAMMING SKILLS













CHARACTER REFERENCE

Computer Science Lecturer (DM45) **UiTM Pahang Branch Raub Campus** (+6012-241 6741) (sitiaisyah@uitm.edu.my)

MUHAMAD SYAHIR ZAKWAN

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a Computer Science student from UiTM Pahang, Raub Campus. I love to code because of the challenges and inspiration to build something awesome. A creative person in designing, attention to detail in my work and very passionate about everything I do. Very young in this field, but that is not a problem for me to learn and gain experience to improve my skill and increase my knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Assistance Black Canyon Coffee | Feb 2019 - Apr 2019

Provide services to the dine-in customer

Web Developer

Universiti Teknologi MARA | May 2021 - July 2021

- Information System Development final year project
- Works with both the front and back ends
- Involve with planning, design and implementation
- Support each other and teach each other teammates

EDUCATION & ACTIVITY

SMK Telok Gadong, Klang Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia | Jan 2017 - Dec 2018

- Pearson LCCI Certificate (Book-keeping & Accounts)
- SPM Excellent Student Award (2018)
- School Prefects (2018)
- Chairman of Fire and Rescue Cadets Malaysia (2018)

Universiti Teknologi MARA, Raub Campus Diploma in Computer Science | Sept 2019 - Present

- Studied OOP, Database, Multimedia, Networking, Security, Web and System Development
- Head of Program & Activity Exco (MARA Youth Technology) Computer Club, MYTECC 2020/2021)
- Event Manager (Jawatankuasa Penamaan Calon Pilihan Raya Kampus 2019)
- Program Director (CyberTech 2021)